clothingemart.com 2010-01-03

# Privacy Policy - Clothing E Mart

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of ClothingeMart.com User Agreement. By using the Sites you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the Sites, you are also consenting to ClothingeMart privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.

##  What Information We Collect

Information You Give Us. The use of certain features and services on the Sites requires that you register and supply personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, telephone number and other information, which is stored by ClothingeMart. When you register as a member of the Sites, we may also collect additional information from you in order to provide you with those specific services and to personalize your experience on the Sites. For example, ClothingeMart.com users may provide more information using. 

##  Use of Information by ClothingeMart.com

Information you provide to us through the Sites is used by ClothingeMart to operate the Sites, provide you with information and services you request, and to communicate with you. We may, for example, send emails to you including newsletters and alerts. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary. You may always choose not to provide us with this information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time. 

##  Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Aggregated Research Data. ClothingeMart produces research reports and other information and data about online shopping for participating merchants, and other customers, as well as media and other interested parties. Such information and data are based on aggregated, anonymous information about millions on online shoppers and do not include any personally identifiable information about individuals. 

##  Content, Ratings and Reviews

Content and Ratings. You can publish reviews, comments and other content. Members can choose to rate products or reviews, and to create a web of trust. As an unregistered visitor, we may allow you to rate products and/or reviews. 

##  Links to Other Sites

The Sites contain links to other web sites. ClothingeMart is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other web sites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site's own privacy policy. 

##  Security

ClothingeMart uses physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including advanced firewall and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.
